Hello traders, this is Paras.  Welcome back to
our channel.  This
is ICICI GI 12 month time frame.  You
can see that the trend line is being formed first from the down side to the upside.
On the six month time frame, we will see that a
trend line is forming from the upside.
On the third month time frame, you will see that a
trend line is being formed.
From the down side to the upside.
On the one month time frame, we will see that it is showing a
flag and pull pattern breakout and retesting.
On the one week time frame, a
parallel trend line is showing on the downside
on the flag and pool pattern and
after the breakout on the flag and pool pattern, it is showing a retest and a
green candle forming again.
On the daily time frame, you will see a
parallel trend line forming from the downside towards the upside
and a resistance level forming from the upside.
On the four-hour time frame, the resistance
level is also
forming. Same as the one-day time frame,
on the one-hour time frame, you can see
that a parallel trend line is forming.
On the 30-minute time frame, you will see that there was a
resistance level zone, which I have moved from
here to here, and the
resistance level is also forming here.
We will wait and see how the resistance level
reacts at this level. A zone is forming here. For
now, this is a no-trading zone
because there has been a big swing here. If the
market breaks out towards the upside, then
you can take a trade in it. The
stop-loss level will be 1879 at this level. The target level will be 1872.
In this,
your target of 1895 will be the next target level.
You will take a trade only on the breakdown of the parallel trend line on the downside of 1909 on the upside.
You will create the second support and can target up to the parallel trend line.  You can place the stop loss level
on its upside parallel trade line.  You will have the same scenario even in 15 time 15 minute time frame.
You will wait for the
market momentum in this.
You should trade only after maintaining your risk reward ratio
and taking advice from a financial advisor.
Thank you so much.